myscrapnook.com 2017-06-06

# 

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR**

**MYSCRAPNOOK™ APPLICATION**

**Last Updated: February 25, 2011**

Welcome to the MyScrapNook™ Application (“MyScrapNook” or “Application) and toolbar (“Toolbar”) (collectively, the “Services”) owned and operated by Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. (“Mindspark”). Mindspark respects the privacy of users of our Services and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. These privacy policies (the "Privacy Policy") are intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the Service the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

**PLEASE NOTE:** Use of the **MyScrapNook Application** is governed by a separate terms of service available [here](http://www.myscrapnook.com/support/tos.html). Use of the Toolbar is governed by the separate End User License Agreement available [here](http://www.myscrapnook.com/support/eula.html).

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the Services or transacting business with us. By using our Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. is a part of the IAC family of businesses ([ _www.iac.com_](http://www.iac.com/)), which includes Ask.com, iWon.com, Girlsense.com, Vimeo.com, Match.com, College Humor, and many others. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

_In General_. We may collect personal information that can identify you, such as your name and email address, and other information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information whether through the Application or by third party network, the information may be sent to servers located in the United States and other countries around the world.

  * **Information you provide.** We may collect and store any personal information you provide to us, including personal information that may be contained in any comment or other submission you post within the Services. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

  * **Information from other sources.** We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from other IAC businesses, business partners, social networks, contractors and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, and additional demographic information. 

    * _**Note about Facebook permissions**_. If you choose to use the Services in connection with Facebook and you choose to set your privacy controls to include “Everyone”, you are granting Facebook permission to share with Mindspark general information about you, including without limitation access to your and your friends' names, profile pictures, gender, user IDs, and connections. Facebook may also make information about the location of your device and your age available to application owners in order to help them implement appropriate security measures and control the distribution of age-appropriate content. We strongly recommend that you review the policies of any social networks you use to make sure you are comfortable with the ways they use information you share with them.

  * **Information about others.** If you use the Services to communicate with others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.), we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient long enough to deliver such message to the intended recipient. 

**Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information**. We use various technologies to collect information from your system and about your interactions with the Services.

  * **Information collected automatically.** We automatically collect information from your system when you visit the Services. This information may include your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address.

  * **Cookies.** When you visit the Application, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our Services and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity within our Services, such as the pages you visit, the links you click, and the actions you take within the Services. Most systems automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline [cookies](http://helpint.mywebsearch.com/intlinfo/privacy/privacy.jhtml), please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on or via the Services.

  * **Other Technologies.** We may use standard Internet technology, such as [web beacons](http://helpint.mywebsearch.com/intlinfo/privacy/privacy.jhtml) and other similar technologies, to track your use of the Services. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our visitors.

  * **Information collected by third-parties.** We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, IAC companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or place ad tags or beacons on our Application or Toolbar. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as [cookies](http://helpint.mywebsearch.com/intlinfo/privacy/privacy.jhtml), to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Unless expressly stated otherwise, we do not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([ _www.networkadvertising.org_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

_In General_. We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver the products and services that you have requested;

  * provide you with customer support

  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our services or content, or products, services or content offered by others;

  * communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our sister IAC companies or other third parties;

  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests;

  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;

  * enforce our terms and conditions;

  * manage our business and

  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

**WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your interaction with our Services.

_Personal information_. We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below. We may share personal information with:

  * **Authorized service providers:** We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our Application functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Services. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

  * **Business partners:** If you engage in promotions offered through the Services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant′s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.

  * **Other IAC businesses.** We are part of the IAC family of businesses (go to [_www.iac.com_](http://www.iac.com/) for a listing of these businesses). We may share information we collect, including personal information, with the IAC companies. Sharing information with our IAC companies enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you.

  * **Other Situations.** We also may disclose your information: 

    * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.

    * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our Application terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.

    * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies which describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

_Aggregated and non-personal information_. We may share aggregated and non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties and our IAC sister companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our Services and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

**THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

There may be places in the Services where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit.

**YOUR CHOICES ABOUT COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

  * You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the Application because such information may be required in order for you to access certain assets or areas; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions with our Services.

  * You may tell us not to share your personal information with third parties or the IAC family of companies for direct marketing purposes by clicking on the following link and entering the email address associated with your account: info@help.myscrapnook.com .

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission′s website at [_http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm_](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm) for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft. 

**CHILDREN** **′** **S PRIVACY**

Our Services are intended for a general audience, over the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**USING OUR SERVICES FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information in the Services from residents of the United States. If you are using the Services outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

**NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES**

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Services.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Application. We recommend that you check this page from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us by email or postal mail as follows:

Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc.  
One North Lexington, 9th Floor  
White Plains, NY, 10601  
ATTN: Privacy Officer/Legal Dept.  

END OF DOCUMENT.

© 2011 Mindspark Interactive Network, Inc. All rights reserved. 

**GLOSSARY:**

Cookies:

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user′s device for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close the Application and is used to make it easier for you to navigate the Application. A persistent cookie remains on your system for an extended period of time.

Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity in our Services, such as the links you click. As the Application does not require a username or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our Services, content and advertising.

We may allow third-parties, including IAC companies, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our Application or Toolbar. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. We do not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party′s privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([ _www.networkadvertising.org_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

Web Beacons:

Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user′s hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may include web beacons in promotional or other e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our Services from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.
